<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://www.trelby.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://www.trelby.org/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-12-11T16:19:08+05:30</updated><id>http://www.trelby.org/</id><title type="html">Trelby</title><subtitle>The free, multiplatform, feature-rich screenwriting program!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Trelby 2.2 released</title><link href="http://www.trelby.org/2012/09/26/trelby-2-2-released/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trelby 2.2 released" /><published>2012-09-26T18:05:49+05:30</published><updated>2012-09-26T18:05:49+05:30</updated><id>http://www.trelby.org/2012/09/26/trelby-2-2-released</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.trelby.org/2012/09/26/trelby-2-2-released/">&lt;p&gt;We are happy to announce the release of Trelby version 2.2. For Windows and Linux binaries, head on over to our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trelby.org/download&quot;&gt;download&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many new features have made it into this release, including the oft-requested undo/redo support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;alignright&quot; src=&quot;/assets/fountain-document-icon-128.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;128&quot; height=&quot;128&quot; /&gt;Trelby now supports importing from and exporting to &lt;a href=&quot;http://fountain.io&quot;&gt;Fountain&lt;/a&gt;, a new markup based screenplay format. We've also added import support for Adobe Story and Fade In Pro. The full details can be seen on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trelby.org/changes&quot;&gt;changes&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We would like to thank Duan Bailey, Bernhard Reiter and Anthony James Huben for their contributions to this release.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We are happy to announce the release of Trelby version 2.2. For Windows and Linux binaries, head on over to our download page. Many new features have made it into this release, including the oft-requested undo/redo support. Trelby now supports importing from and exporting to Fountain, a new markup based screenplay format. We've also added import support for Adobe Story and Fade In Pro. The full details can be seen on the changes page. We would like to thank Duan Bailey, Bernhard Reiter and Anthony James Huben for their contributions to this release.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trelby 2.1 released</title><link href="http://www.trelby.org/2012/03/26/trelby-2-1-released/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trelby 2.1 released" /><published>2012-03-26T06:07:13+05:30</published><updated>2012-03-26T06:07:13+05:30</updated><id>http://www.trelby.org/2012/03/26/trelby-2-1-released</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.trelby.org/2012/03/26/trelby-2-1-released/">&lt;p&gt;We are happy to announce the release of Trelby version 2.1. This release is dedicated to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.scriptfrency.org&quot;&gt;Script Frenzy&lt;/a&gt;, the non-profit that conducts the annual screenwriting frenzy in the month of April.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New features in 2.1 include PDF watermarking support, Celtx import support, and many more. The full details can be seen on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trelby.org/changes&quot;&gt;changes&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Windows and Linux binaries, head on over to our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trelby.org/download&quot;&gt;download&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We are happy to announce the release of Trelby version 2.1. This release is dedicated to Script Frenzy, the non-profit that conducts the annual screenwriting frenzy in the month of April. New features in 2.1 include PDF watermarking support, Celtx import support, and many more. The full details can be seen on the changes page. For Windows and Linux binaries, head on over to our download page.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Announcing Trelby</title><link href="http://www.trelby.org/2012/01/02/announcing-trelby/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Announcing Trelby" /><published>2012-01-02T13:17:05+05:30</published><updated>2012-01-02T13:17:05+05:30</updated><id>http://www.trelby.org/2012/01/02/announcing-trelby</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.trelby.org/2012/01/02/announcing-trelby/">&lt;p&gt;We are happy to announce the release of Trelby 2.0, a simple, free and multi-platform screenwriting program. Rather than restating the feature list, why not head over to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trelby.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;homepage&lt;/a&gt; and take a look at all the features Trelby has to offer! Or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trelby.org/download&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;download it&lt;/a&gt; for your platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trelby is the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trelby.org/about&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;rebranding of an older&lt;/a&gt; screenwriting program called Blyte, a one-man effort by Osku Salerma, from 2006. The code was open sourced, but did not gain any new developers until October 2011, when Anil Gulecha jumped in being &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gulecha.org/2012/01/02/presenting-trelby/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;dissatisfied with available&lt;/a&gt; screenwriting options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trelby is free software, released under the GPL free software license. Take a look at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trelby.org/contribute&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;contribute page&lt;/a&gt; for more information on how to get involved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We are happy to announce the release of Trelby 2.0, a simple, free and multi-platform screenwriting program. Rather than restating the feature list, why not head over to the homepage and take a look at all the features Trelby has to offer! Or download it for your platform. Trelby is the rebranding of an older screenwriting program called Blyte, a one-man effort by Osku Salerma, from 2006. The code was open sourced, but did not gain any new developers until October 2011, when Anil Gulecha jumped in being dissatisfied with available screenwriting options. Trelby is free software, released under the GPL free software license. Take a look at the contribute page for more information on how to get involved.</summary></entry></feed>